I started out teaching millennials. I'm
a millennial.
We had the decency to talk behind
our teachers' backs.
As the universe intended.
Gen Z
right to your face all day.
And when you think you know what you
look like,
they hit you with new information
>> [laughter]
>> about your face you've had your whole
life.
One day a girl looked right at me, she
said, "Hey miss, your eyebrows are off."
I said, "Hey, I paid to have them look
this way.
>> [laughter]
>> How are they off? I'll let my
aesthetician know."
And she replied, "I don't know, they're
just not giving."
>> [laughter]
>> I said,
"What are they not giving?
>> [laughter]
>> I'll let my waxer know."
And this sweet quiet kid who never said
anything blurted out symmetry.
>> [laughter]
>> And that hurt my feelings because
>> that was new information.
Spent the whole day just looking at my
face, but like this.
>> [laughter]